{
    "subject": "resource/Sidney_Toler",
    "predicate": "ontology/deathYear",
    "object": "1947",
    "human_readable": "Sidney Toler died in 1947.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.970112144947052,
            "question": "Was Sidney Toler alive in the year 1948?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9233524203300476,
            "question": "When did Sidney Toler die?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8742847442626953,
            "question": "In what year was Sidney Toler deceased?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8282824754714966,
            "question": "What year marks the death of Sidney Toler?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.767055094242096,
            "question": "How long ago did Sidney Toler die?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6799452304840088,
            "question": "What is the significance of the year 1947 regarding Sidney Toler?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6448177099227905,
            "question": "To what year are we referring when talking about Sidney Toler's death?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.625342071056366,
            "question": "If today was 2023, would Sidney Toler be alive?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5764697790145874,
            "question": "When did Sidney Toler pass away?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.3971509039402008,
            "question": "What is the date of Sidney Toler's passing?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Sidney Toler died in 1947.",
            "html": "dbpedia_1960_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=When did Sidney Toler pass away?",
            "html": "dbpedia_1960_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=If today was 2023, would Sidney Toler be alive?",
            "html": "dbpedia_1960_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=To what year are we referring when talking about Sidney Toler's death?",
            "html": "dbpedia_1960_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1960_21.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1960_4.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1960_45.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1960_48.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1960_52.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1960_54.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1960_59.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1960_72.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1960_73.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1960_85.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "{'output': 'yes'}"
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\"output\": \"yes\"}\n```\n\nThe documents provide information that confirms Sidney Toler died on February 12, 1947. Therefore, the statement \"Sidney Toler died in 1947\" is supported by the given context."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "The Least Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}